[
  {
    "id": "a0001",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "1",
    "question": "Chronic poor calcium intake results in",
    "correctAnswer": "Osteoarthritis",
    "optionValues": [
      "Osteoarthritis",
      "Osteoporosis",
      "Sarcopenia",
      "Rickets"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0002",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "1",
    "question": "_______________  contains iron but is exclusively found in muscles",
    "correctAnswer": "Myoglobin",
    "optionValues": [
      "Hemoglobin",
      "Albumin",
      "Myoglobin",
      "Ferritin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0003",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "1",
    "question": "Vegetarianism and alcohol abuse impairs ___________ absorption",
    "correctAnswer": "Zinc",
    "optionValues": [
      "Vitamin B6",
      "Vitamin B12",
      "Zinc",
      "Selenium"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0004",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "1",
    "question": "The AI for fluoride  for adult women is __________ mg/ day",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "optionValues": [
      "6",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0005",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "1",
    "question": "RDA for selenium older than 55 yrs of age is _______mcg/ day",
    "correctAnswer": "55",
    "optionValues": [
      "45",
      "35",
      "65",
      "55"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0006",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "1",
    "question": "____________ is a common side effect of prescription drugs",
    "correctAnswer": "Anorexia",
    "optionValues": [
      "Anosmia",
      "Anorexia",
      "Gingivits",
      "Dementia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0007",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "1",
    "question": "___________ contributes to malnutrition in  older individuals",
    "correctAnswer": "Loneliness",
    "optionValues": [
      "Retirement",
      "Loneliness",
      "Rejection",
      "Worthlessness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0008",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "1",
    "question": "Which of these  is not a sensory aspect of food selection?",
    "correctAnswer": "Mental status",
    "optionValues": [
      "Mental status",
      "Appetite",
      "Taste acuity",
      "Anosmia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0009",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "1",
    "question": "__________ is a  stronger determinant of food choice",
    "correctAnswer": "Perceived health benefit",
    "optionValues": [
      "Perceived health benefit",
      "Convenience",
      "Price",
      "Prestige value"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0010",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "1",
    "question": "Nutritional supplements are important in  meeting needs of patients with ______________",
    "correctAnswer": "Advanced SDAT",
    "optionValues": [
      "Diabetes",
      "Insomnia",
      "Depression",
      "Advanced SDAT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0011",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "2",
    "question": "DHEA is produced in the thyroid gland",
    "correctAnswer": "False",
    "optionValues": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0012",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "2",
    "question": "Lower esophageal  sphincter relaxes in pharyngeal phase",
    "correctAnswer": "False",
    "optionValues": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0013",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "2",
    "question": "Conduction of neural impulses requires release of dopamine",
    "correctAnswer": "True",
    "optionValues": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0014",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "2",
    "question": "The skin and respiratory tract secrete antimicrobial peptides such as catalase",
    "correctAnswer": "False",
    "optionValues": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0015",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "2",
    "question": "Passive immunity can be generated by vaccination",
    "correctAnswer": "False",
    "optionValues": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0016",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "2",
    "question": "Increased release of erythropoietin may contribute to anemia in elderly",
    "correctAnswer": "False",
    "optionValues": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0017",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "2",
    "question": "Pharmacodynamics refers to the effect of drugs on target organs",
    "correctAnswer": "True",
    "optionValues": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0018",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "2",
    "question": "Cardiac glycosides cause diarrhea accompanied by nausea",
    "correctAnswer": "False",
    "optionValues": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0019",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "2",
    "question": "MAO inhibitors are prescribed as anti - depressants",
    "correctAnswer": "True",
    "optionValues": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "a0020",
    "type": "radio",
    "category": "2",
    "question": "In Cardiovascular disease the cerebral blood flow can be decreased by 30% and renal blood flow by as much as 45%",
    "correctAnswer": "True",
    "optionValues": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  }
]